[Silent laughter]
This is so good pranks.
-Boom!
We prank.
-Prank channel.
First we took you there with the camper ... -Yes yes.
Then Niklas went on it.
Soon he will come in again with an ax and threatens Niklas.
[In chorus] just that.
Because it's his brides.
We will react to this.
-Ah.
We have no idea how the blind dating has gone for Niklas.
-No.
Anton who helped film this has cut this together as a draft and we will see how the hell is.
In another room, so we didn't see this.
-No what it was wrong.
On each other.
This, we may say is a little fiveish thing and what are the others called ...?
-Sidemen
But we hook it up, we test.
-Yes Yes.
They are so damn awesome at it so we, we test.
[Casted Voice] Fucking Copycat, that is.
Check out Nikla's reaction now.
No No Niklas.
Yes, drive!
So Niklas is a new single.
It's fun that Anton cut that music, because it's like Niklas never met a girl in his life
What should ....?
Yes!
There will be lots of girls and you will date them.
One of these could be your future wife, Niklas.
I'm in shock ...
Sit there.
-Do I do this?
I was sweating now.
[Out of picture] Yes.
This is how it will work now: you ask these questions ...
Now check, the legs just bounce.
... and then based on their response, which is the worst, so you say "No, number Tres answers I don't like ..."
Disappear.
How to send her out.
So there is one left, and you have to marry it.
Oh, he jerks.
[Laughter, nonsense sound]
He couldn't keep up.
[LAUGH]
Looked like he was standing and toxin.
-No, but he probably did.
Now comes the brides.
-I just have to check.
What happened there?
[Laughter] does he piss?
Here comes the brides yes.
Here they come.
[Expectant music] -I can't cope.
He couldn't stay for three minutes.
Down there is Annie, she may recognize from Tiktok.
Also from Kungsbacka.
So is Niklas.
What the hell?
Do you know what the fun is?
I think Niklas decided to be hard from the beginning.
I do not know what it is.
[Niklas says something outside the room] -Ye?
What did you say Niklas?
He is outside and panic now.
[Niklas] She fucking bitten my pants ...
A little funfact: He has brought one of the brides to the office now because they are together.
She is completely crazy and has broken his pants.
Has she broken her pants?
-Angie?
Try to leave her.
-She just jumps around.
Oh damn.
-It's always so at the beginning of a relationship Niklas.
Was it Angie he talked about?
-Yes.
Damn.
Now Stella has bitten..Ah ...
She can't calm down ...
Eat and eat, that's what I had to give.
-I would say we sit down at a bar.
Then we run a blue and white match at Ullevi.
Then maybe if it gets a little, ah ... feeling then maybe you go to a hotel room.
Have a little good or so maybe.
Hole bunch?
-Why does it look like Niklas wants to shoot himself in the head every time they answer?
He is backwards.
He doesn't want to talk about alcohol.
Why doesn't he smile?
He looks very happy.
-He is nervous.
Look at him.
-He is nervous yes.
He sweats.
-Or is this Niklas when he's happy?
... orders drinks for each other.
A little fun to see what you have for a drink the first date I think.
Number six.
I'm probably thinking ... -
Drink flavor?
So, I order a Bloody Mary for you.
Well, it's not that it's an ice .. -Then it must be really sick drinks.
It is if anyone pulls ten Long Island, then maybe you are like this "you and I" but about anyone ...
Does it really happen?
-Number two has done it a lot of times.
Do you think so?
-Yes that can probably happen often.
It feels like you do it if you are properly packed.
Had I been single, I would have been the worst at picking up.
Incredibly bad.
-Rag me once.
It's a penny now.
Sit there.
I am a bartender.
Should you have raw juice?
[Light voice] I'm so damn horny!
[Laughter] -What did he say?
Horny?
Huh?
-You stand with the bartender?
I do not know why...
I thought she was there, it is three o'clock at night ...
We start over.
-Okay.
Then it was a raw juice for you here.
-Yes thank you.
Well can yes beat me down here?
[CONSIDERED VOOK] Okay.
What did you say?
-Okay.
I think you are incredibly nice.
Your beard, how thick it is.
Eh ... may I offer something to drink?
Yes, I want a tequila sunrise.
Do you want a tequila Sunrise?
Does she say so?
Is that the first thing ...?
"Do you want something to drink? Yes a Tequila Sunrise" [laughs to]
I thought she likes it.
Is it Conchita Wurst?
- Mmm.
Imagine your fucking beard.
Had I met a girl with that beard ...
Imagine what a beard, but also think which cock.
Okay....
We are on the second question.
-Number four.
Tjena biscuit, do you stand there and crumble? [Giggle]
I can't pick up unfortunately, that's why I'm here.
That was a good answer.
-Number five, eh ...
Why is everything going so fast here?
They ask no question except "Do you regret your choice?"
"yes!"
I think it's nervousness.
-Yes, nervousness.
They just want to go from there.
Appearance?
Blonde, 25 years, like to sport ...
Gym cod preferably, I like to work out.
-She looked stiff.
I like blonde guys, so I'm not so ... the look doesn't matter that much, but a little long-
Blonde guys.
Does she know that it is Niklas on the other side?
We had printed that the guy is blonde.
Advantage for her.
Smart girl anyway!
Femman has very clear requirements.
-Yes, preferences.
Could that be why she is single?
You have to think what you want, but it limits ... -very specifically.
You limit most of the world.
It feels like she has very high demands.
You recognize that in people who are singles with too high demands, they never meet anyone.
You have to lower the garden a little.
Uppercut.
-Red in the kidney.
I like long guys, preferably over 1.90.
-There it happened.
It's a plus, but no dealbreaker.
They may like to have brown hair,
I have blond hair myself so don't think it's as-sexy with someone who looks like me.
He will send her now.
-Thered broad -axled.
It is also a plus at the edge.
I'm not so picky, so I would say nice eyes ...
Get a good burn for the summer ... tattoos are najs.
It is this classic.
"I'm not so picky ... but preferably nice eyes ..." -"Good pigment, tattoos"
Yes exactly.
[LAUGH]
Money, housing ... -Abs.
[Added] "can imagine skipping cohabitation agreements"
"23 Slak"
"Contacts ..." Yes, just that.
I think he will send Annie now, number 6. -I
It described the opposite of Niklas.
I think he likes number seven.
There are things I don't like, but ...
You will know that if you are so fortunate, I think.
Number seven then ... you have to explore it a little yourself.
-Good answer.
But I would never drive anal.
[Girl] anal?
Nah.
Feet go away.
No foot fetish here.
It was exciting answers.
I send number six home.
Ouch.
Hello!
Annie.
Do you regret?
-Yes I do.
But I think like this: Aj .... Oww.
Then we match a little.
-Okay,
I choose to send home ... I think it was number five.
Danny Saucedo?
-No!
Then I send home the one that was before.
No!
He changed.
-Do you regret?
Eh, no I don't.
[Upset] No but I can't cope!
-"Ah okay..."
Everyone is very nice and cute after all.
[Done] in its own way!
I think everyone is really nice!
-Yes, but ...
He must be honest.
-He can't say he regrets all.
You get a little pain in the heart.
-Yes.
Such a sad guy ... -No!
Was she sad there?
But it's not a fetish, I have none.
Like this.
Check it out.
[Groaning silently]
Did you get goose?
- Yes it was ...
Also have no fetish.
Number seven, by the way.
But if I have to say something then when the guy is good at taking command, have some good confidence.
[Barsian] Now you take the disk I tell you!
[Laughter] and then so ...
[Laughter] And after that you cook or!
And then we jump in the chamber!
A little hybris maybe.
Number eight.
My students will see this ... when you are a little hard -handed maybe.
-Teacher?
But damn ... why are you looking into the camera like that?
When you said that.
-Is she teacher?
[Mimics] "My students will see this ... a little hard -handed maybe?"
See you certainly some other day.
-Yes we do that safely.
What is required for your parents ... -come again now!
He is a little golden boy.
I flush back a bit.
-Winga Niklas!
What is required for your parents to like me?
Big cock.
-Okay number seven then.
I think it's kind of treating me well and having a good job type.
Dad is so: "Good job".
For me, it is most important that my nephews like you.
And if you are good with children, you go home as well.
-FIN response.
But my mom, she is very easy.
So humor, type.
My mom is pretty easy to be taken with,
She changed now!
-As she?
She said Dad said good job?
-Yes exactly!
"Good job and treat me with respect," she said.
And just because she changed and family "yes humor, family, mom ..."
[Made] Yes and that everyone is the same and safe in the family!
And that you like brother's kids.
She has no nephews.
-I am a little family girl so.
Changes altogether.
[Made] and I love short blonde guys ... so.
I have dogs so it's important that they like you.
But they are kind, so ... -How many then?
My dog just bit his pants.
Hello!
Hanna.
Do you regret?
Eh no.
[Shocked sound]
[Dramatic sound] Aaah!
Starting to run around ... [laughter]
"Do you regret? No. [Dramatic sound]"
[High sound] -she couldn't take it.
Damn, she expected him to say yes, maybe.
There is only one left.
No ... It wasn't good.
It will be such a Big Reveal now.
There is only one left now, so we can see who it is.
Hi, Angelica.
-Niklas, do you get a hug?